Hey Dan, we finished the settings. Do you want to check it out?
>> Oh, great.
>> Wait. What's with all this stuff right here?
>> I'm glad you asked. All this stuff will help me demonstrate the
power of implicit intents. Leveraging other
apps to get functionality for your app
for fee. For example, why would you write a bar code scanning app,
when you can just launch an intent to do it for you. [SOUND].
>> Or a camera app, where you can just launch
an intent to fire a photo. [SOUND] And of course, it would make no sense to
write a phone app just to dial a phone number, you would just call the intent.
>> Wait, I need that.
>> In other words, don't reinvent the wheel. Lazy programmers make fewer
mistakes. Now, let's go implement an
implicit intent. Raydo? Dan's being implicit again.